rwandair.com 2014-09-26

# Rwandair - Fly our Dream to the Heart of Africa.

RwandAir has established industry-standard measures to ensure the safety of your personal information and will continuously improve on them. Personal information provided on rwandair.com, the website for which these standards are set, are only used and processed to the extent necessary for RwandAir to fulfill its obligations to you, and/or to comply with our legal obligations. For the purpose of the policies below, "Personal Information" shall be defined as detailed in the Promotion of Access to Information Act of 2000 (PAIA). The PAIA may be downloaded from [http://www.polity.org.za/attachment...](http://www.polity.org.za/attachment.php?aa_id=3569)

RwandAir does NOT store or keep your personal information in its servers, but rather relies on a secure storage environment that meets the safest industry standards to protect and keep your personal information out of reach from any unauthorized third party. RwandAir may request that you disclose certain information for the particular purpose of the obligation being undertaken such as an online transaction, an account with Dream MilesÃ¢â€žÂ¢ frequent flyer program, a subscription to our newsletter, a registration to an event, etc. You may be requested to provide certain personal identifiable information such as your name, address, telephone numbers, fax numbers, email address and/or debit/credit card details including billing address, passport number and nationality. RwandAir may access some of this information for the purpose of its customer management services. You have the right to access, change, and oppose any information that concerns you (read "Use of your Personal Information" below). In the event that you wish to exercise your right, please contact us at the address provided below.

RwandAir reserves the right to update or modify the Privacy Policy, at any time and without prior notice, by posting the revised version of the Policy onrwandair.com. If we decide to change and/or modify our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on rwandair.com so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you by way of an email. If you so wish, you may withdraw your consent to such use subject to and in accordance with the terms of our Privacy Policy. USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION As a general policy, RwandAir does NOT collect personal identifiable information. However, if you wish to use a certain service or product available onrwandair.com, or receive information, or participate in a program, you will be asked to provide certain information in order to process your request. In the event that such service or product is provided through a partnership with a third party, your personal information will NOT be collected by the said party on our behalf. RwandAir may disclose your information to a third party ONLY in order to fulfill its obligation to you, or to comply with our legal duties. For such cases, RwandAir will notify you and request your consent before proceeding. RwandAir shall take all reasonable steps to protect the personal information on the website.

Records of your activity or transactions will be stored alongside your personal information as you keep using our products/services on rwandair.com. These records will only serve in the management and administration of the services rendered to you and will help enhance your overall online experience. ACCESS TO PERSONAL INFORMATION You have the right to access, change and oppose any action on your personal information at any time. If you no longer wish to disclose your personal information to us you may opt-out of our services for which personal information is collected. But remember, doing so may hinder our abilities to fulfill our obligation(s) to you, or exercise good servicing to you.

Access to historical records associated with your personal information may be availed to you for free (at no charge) or for a nominal fee. CREDIT CARD SECURITY All credit card transactions are processed by and via our payment processing partner PayGate (Pty) Ltd. PayGate also stores your credit card information in their secure environment. RwandAir does NOT store and process your credit card information. Credit card transactions will be acquired for RwandAir via PayGate (Pty) Ltd who are the approved payment gateway for Standard Bank of South Africa, our merchant account host. The merchant outlet country at the time of presenting payment options is South Africa. The transaction currency is United States Dollar ($US). However, this website is governed by the laws of Rwanda.

PayGate uses industry-standard data encryption to protect your online transaction, namely SSL3 (Secure Socket Layer 3). You may visit PayGate website to view their security certificate and policies. RwandAir takes responsibility for all aspects relating to the transaction including sale of goods and services sold on this website, customer services and support, dispute resolutions and delivery of goods.

For even more security, you may visit your respective card manufacturer’s website and complete the additional security measures provided, such asMasterCardÃ‚Â® Secure CodeÃ¢â€žÂ¢ or VisaÃ‚Â® Verified By VisaÃ¢â€žÂ¢. For more information, please contact us at this address : RwandAir, Kigali International Airport, top floor. P.O. Box 7275 Kigali, Rwanda. AttneCommerce and Online Marketing, Commercial Department. Support email : support@rwandair.com Support telephone : +250-252 503687 Fax : +250- 252 503686
